Register of the Stanley Kuhl Hornbeck papers, 1900-1966
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject and Correspondence File, 1842-1966 (Boxes 1-452)
  - Paris Peace Conference
    - Lansing at Paris
    - League of Nations, China on
    - League of Nations, Covenant
    - League of Nations and Far East
    - League of Nations, Japan on
    - League of Nations, Memo on Russia
    - Loan program, China
    - Luxembourg, in the Treaty
    - Makino on Japan's intentions on Shantung, 1919 May 4
    - Millard, T. F., "China's Case at the Peace Conference"
    - Most-Favored-Nation Clause, memo to Young
    - Multilateral conventions, list of
    - Newspaper articles (Box 330)
    - Official Directory of the Paris Peace Conference
    - Official orders, miscellaneous
    - Omsk Government, reasons for recognizing
    - Pacific Islands, Blakeslee, "Former German Pacific Possessions"
    - Pacific Islands, disposal of
    - Pacific Islands, problem of
    - Personnel
    - Political Science, Ecole Libre, Paris
    - Race question
    - Reception
    - Recommendations, official (complete)
    - Recommendations, on "Racial Equality"
    - Siberia
    - Siberia, Kolchak Government
    - Treaty Clauses
    - Treaty with Germany, Peace, Temps Resume
    - Treaty, Presentation of
    - Williams, E. T., letter to President
    - Willoughby program
    - Weale, Putnam, "Asia" article
    - Weale, Putnam, program
    - Young, Memo on Open Door to
    - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1919-1920; 4.0 folders) (Box 331)
    - House "Inquiry" Group
    - House Inquiry, photo
    - Parker, Frank (Box 332)
  - Parker, Philo W.
  - Parkin, G. R.
  - Parkin, Raleigh, 1963
  - Parrott, Robert (Durley), AKA
  - Parrott, Col. Robert P.
  - Parsons, Charles E.
  - Parsons, President Edward S., Baccalaureate
  - Partridge, Maj. Gen. Earle E.
  - Party for Justices, Diplomatic Corps, 1946 April 29
  - Party Platforms, 1932
  - Party Platforms, 1952
  - Paschal, George R., Jr.
  - Passports
  - Pasvolsky, Leo
  - Patchin, P. H.
  - Patterson, Ambassador
  - Patterson, Jefferson
  - Patterson, Richard C., Jr.
  - Patterson, William L.
  - Patton, C. W.
  - Patton, General George S.
  - Patton, General George S., death, 1945
  - Patton, Kenneth S.
  - Pawley, William D.
  - Paxton, J. Hall
  - Payer, Harry F.
  - Payne, Thomas
  - Peace, general (Box 333)
  - Peace, 1930, 1943-1944
  - Peace Corps
  - Peace machinery (Box 334)
  - Peace plans
  - Peace Planning Subcommittee, 1940
  - Peace proposals
  - Peace terms
  - Pearl Harbor
  - Pearl Harbor, Department of State and events of December 7, 1941
  - Pearl Harbor (4 folders) (Box 335)
  - Pearl Harbor (special), 1945
  - Pearl Harbor, Kimmel, Admiral Husband, his "Own Story of...,", 1954 December (Box 336)
  - Peace machinery (Box 334)
  - Pearl Harbor, Captain Kittredge, 1954
  - Pearl Harbor, photostatic copies of Japanese newspapers
  - Pearl Harbor, Theobald, etc.
  - Pearls (W. and L.)
  - Pearson, Drew
  - Pearson story, 1944
  - Peaslee, Amos J.
  - Peck, Willys, 1928-1936; 3.0 folders)
  - Peck, Willys R. (2 folders), 1937-1942 (Box 337)
  - Peffer, Nathaniel, 2.0 folders)
  - Pegler, Westbrook
  - Pegram, Colonel J. C.
  - Pehle, John
  - Peking American School, S. K. Hornbeck at, lectures, 1926
  - The Peking Leader
  - Peking luncheon, 1925
  - Pelenyi, John
  - Pell, Robert T.
  - Penfield, J. K.
  - Penick, Bessie
  - People
  - People, race problems
  - Perkins, Mahlon F.
  - Permanent Court of Arbitration
  - Permanent Court of International Justice (World Court)
  - Perry, Matthew C., Addresses on, by S. K. Hornbeck (Box 338)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton
  - Perry Treaty, Eighteenth Anniversary, Bankers Club, New York, 1934 April 11
  - Persia, "Where Civilization Was Cradled"
  - Personnel
  - Peter, W. W.
  - Peters, Nellie
  - Peterson, Hugh
  - Petroleum
    - General
    - Bibliography and articles (Box 339)
    - Japan and the Netherlands East India
    - Monopoly, Japanese
    - Standard Vacuum Oil Company, 4.0 folders)
    - Standard Oil Offices, discussions with, 1934-1936 (Box 340)
    - Struggle for Petroleum, Institute of Politics, Williamstown, Massachusetts, August 7, 1923
  - Pettengill, Admiral
  - Petty, R. Moulton
  - Pettus, W. B.
  - Pfeiffer, C. G.
  - Pforzheimer, Carl H., Jr.
  - Phelps, G. Sidney
  - Phelps, Admiral W. W. (U.S.N., retired)
  - Phenix, Spencer
  - Phi Beta Kappa, Speech at Cincinnati, 1937
  - Phi Beta Kappa and American Foreign Policy - Philadelphia, 1928
  - Philadelphia (academy) See also: Speeches and Writings: China (Box 341)
  - Philip Morris & Co., Ltd., Inc.
  - Philippine Islands
    - General
    - Aviation
    - Bibliography
    - Clippings
    - Clippings and pamphlets
    - Clippings and pamphlets (Box 342)
    - Commercial and trade relations, 2.0 folders)
    - Commissioner, High
    - Commissioner in United States, resident
    - Defense (Box 343)
    - General
    - Government
    - Government, 2.0 folders) (Box 344)
    - Immigration
    - Independence
    - Neutralization of
    - Office
    - President of (Box 345)
    - Public works
    - Question of Naval Base, 1937
    - U.S. Naval Base
    - U.S. Relations, Postwar
    - Wood-Forbes Report, 1921
  - Phillips, Alfred N.
  - Phillips, Beatrice
  - Phillips, Wallace B.
  - Phillips, William
  - Phraner, Stanley L.
  - Pickel, Robert D.
  - Picot, Madame Willie Georges
  - Pierce Arrow Service
  - Pierson, Warren Lee
  - Piffard, Helen Strong
  - Pilcher, James B.
  - Pillion, John R.
  - Pillsbury Flour Mills Company
  - Pinchot, Mrs. Gifford
  - Pinon, Rene, "A New Phase of the Struggle for the Pacific"
  - Pitcher, Stephen L.
  - Pittman, Key
  - Plane (Box 346)
  - Planes
  - Plans and suggestions
  - Platforms, United States Government Party, 1940, 1944
  - Plattsburg
  - Pledges
  - Pleiss, Walter
  - Plesman, Albert
  - Podoski, Victor
  - Poems
  - Pogue, Joseph E.
  - Poland, W. B.
  - Poland
  - Police
  - Police Force, International
  - Police, traffic, May 29, 1955
  - Policy Committee
    - Policy Committee
    - Minutes, 1943-1944
    - Minutes, 1943-1944 (3 folders) (Box 347-348)
  - Polish Embassy (Box 349)
  - Polish Information Service
  - Political economy
  - Political psychology
  - Political Science
  - Political Science Association (D.C.)
  - Political Science, general, outline
  - Political Science, Study of
  - Politics
  - Politics, Science of, Report of National Conference on, 1923
  - Pond, J. Lawrence
  - Pontillo, Nick
  - Pool, John C.
  - Poole, Dewitt C.
  - Poon Lim
  - Poor, Henry V.
  - Pope, Arthur Upham
  - Population
  - Population, world
  - Populations and territories, Japanese controlled
  - Porter, Catherine (Box 350)
  - Porter, Congressman Charles O. and Nash, Ernest T.
  - Porter, Lucius
  - Porter, Ruth
  - Porter, Stephen G.
  - Porter, Thurston R.
  - Portsmouth Treaty
  - Portugal
  - Portuguese Legation
  - Pos, Mary
  - Possony, Stefan T.
  - Post Office Department
  - Post offices
  - Posthumus, N. W.
  - Postman
  - Post-War
  - Post-War Foreign Policy, Advisory Committee on
  - Post-War Foreign Policy, Advisory Council on
  - Post-War planning, commitments and aims
  - Post-War Programs, Committee on (Box 351)
  - Potsdam Papers
  - Potsdam, Tripartite at Berlin, 1945 July 17 - August 2
  - Pott, F. L. Hawks
  - Potter, Kenneth F.
  - Potter, Pitman B.
  - Pouch Service
  - Pound, Roscoe, on U.S. China Policy, 1949
  - Poverty
  - Powell, Helen K.
  - Powell, J. B.
  - Powell, Nancy
  - Powell, P. P.
  - Powell, Ralph, 1960
  - Power, effective rulers of the Untied States
  - Powers, John H.
  - Poynter, Nelson P.
  - Pratt, John H.
  - Pratt, Sir John
  - Precedent
  - Predictions
  - Preparedness
    - Problems of, 1916; 3.0 folders)
    - Figures, 1917 (Box 352)
    - 1917 material
    - U.S. Army and Navy Chart, 1917
    - W. R. Castle, Armistice Day speech, 1930
    - 1915-1935
    - 1934
    - 1936-1944 (Box 353)
    - 1945
    - 1966
    - Pamphlets
  - President's Message
  - President's Messages, 1917
  - President Polk's Proclamation of War with Mexico (1846)
    See also: China: Papers: Reinsch acquisition
  - President's Statement to Congress, 1914 December 15
  - Presidents of the United States, The Book of the
  - Press
  - Press clipping bureaus (Box 354)
  - Press conferences
  - Press (the), Dillon, E. J. on
  - Press, French
  - "Press and Politics," Volume I, Number 1
  - Press (the), 1956
  - Price, Allen Thomas
  - Price, Ben
  - Price, Elizabeth Kendall
  - Price, Ernest B.
  - Price, Frank
  - Price, Harry B., "The Marshall Plan"
  - Price, Harry B.
  - Price, Maurice T.
  - Price, Willard
  - Prickett, Karl E.
  - Princeton, 1930
  - Princeton, 1938 December 3
  - Princeton, 20th Century Fund, Ronald Reagan, 1954-1955
  - Princeton School of Public and International Affairs
  - Principles
  - Principles of U.S. foreign policy
  - Prisoners of war
  - Prisoners of war, circa 1944 (Box 355)
  - Prisoners of war, Execution of Aviators
    See also: Doolittle Raid
  - Private property, immunity in war
  - Progress
  - Prohibition
  - Propaganda, 2.0 folders)
  - Propaganda Committee, Combined Chiefs of Staff
  - Propaganda, methods, Parker
  - Property list, estate
  - Prophecies
  - Prophecies, 1940-1943
  - Prophecy
  - Prophesying
  - Protection of American Interests (Box 356)
  - "Protection of Citizens Abroad by Armed Force," by Edwin Borchard
  - Protection of foreign interests
  - Protocol
  - Protocol, Diplomatic Reception, White House, 1936-1937
  - Protocol (Geneva) for Pacific Settlement of International Disputes, 1924
  - Protocol, Washington, list of rank and precedence, 1953
  - Providence Journal and Evening Bulletin
  - Prussian Treaty of 1828
  - Pruzzle contest
  - Psychology
  - Psychopolitics
  - Pu Yi
  - Public Action
  - Public Affairs Press
  - Public opinion
  - Publicity
  - Publisher
  - Puckle, Sir Frederick
  - Puerto Rico
  - Pugach, Noel (U. of Wisconsin)
  - Puleston, William D.
  - Puleston, "The Influence of Force in Foreign Relations,", 1955
  - Purdy, Milton D.
  - Puryear, Edward F.
  - Putnam, John R.
  - G. P. Putnam's Sons
  - Quaker Oats Company (Box 357)
  - Quarantine
  - Quemoy
  - Quemoy and Matsu, ABC's of, 1958
  - Quezon, Manuel
  - Quigley, Harold S.
    - General, 2.0 folders)
    - Articles
      See also: China: Quigley, Harold S., articles by
    - "Chinese Politics and Foreign Powers,", 1927
    - Chinese Politics Today, Review, 1934 May
    - University of Minneapolis, 1934
  - Quillian, Fletcher
  - Quittner, Joseph
  - Quo Tai-chi, Dr.
  - Quotations ("Thoughts")
  - Quotations and stories
  - Rabbitt, James A. (Box 358)
  - Rabindranath, Tagore
  - Race question
  - Races and problems
  - Racial equality
  - Radio station, International Settlement, Shanghai
  - Radio station, Mukden
  - Radio, U.S.
  - Railway, Burma - Yunnan
  - Railway, Chesapeake and Ohio
  - Railway, Chicago, Rhode Island and Pacific Railway Co.
  - Railway, Trans-Siberian
  - Rajchman, Ludwik
  - Rakhit, Hemendra K.
  - Ramos, Carlos
  - Ramsay, Gordon A.
  - Rand, Elbridge D.
  - Randolph, Bessie C.
  - Rankin, Jeannette (Montana)
  - Rankin, Karl L.
  - Ranneft, J. W. Meijer
  - Ransdell, J. H.
  - Rappaport, Armin
  - Raven, F. J.
  - Ravndal, C. M.
  - Raw materials
  - Rawls, Fletcher
  - Ray, J. Franklin
  - Rayl, L. B.
  - Raymond, Allen
  - Rayner, Charles B.
  - Rea, George Bronson
  - Read, Thomas T. (Box 359)
  - Reader's Digest
  - Ready, Michael J. (Monsignor)
  - Reagan, Ronald
  - Real estate and moving, 1938
  - Realism
  - Realities
  - Rearick, Elizabeth
  - Reber, Samuel
  - Reciprocity and Preferential Tariff Systems
  - Recognition
  - Recognition of governments, Hornbeck on, ASIL, 1950
  - Recording machine
  - Records of usage
  - Red Cross
  - Red Cross, American
  - Red Cross Congress in Japan, Judge Payne, delegate, 1934
  - Redistribution
  - Reed, Harold and Alice
  - Reed, Martha
  - Reed, Stanley
  - Reener, J. S.
  - Refugee Economic Corporation
  - Refugees, political
  - Reid, Gilbert (Box 360)
  - Reid, John Gilbert
  - Reifsnider, Bishop C. S.
  - Reilly, Brig. Gen. Henry J. (U.S.A., retired)
  - Reinsch, Paul S., 7.0 folders)
  - Reischauer, Edwin O. (Box 361)
  - Relations
    - China - France
    - China - Russia
    - France - Great Britain
    - France - U.S.
    - Great Britain - Netherlands
    - Japan - Netherlands
    - Japan - U.S.S.R.
    - U.S. - China
    - U.S. - Great Britain
    - U.S. - Japan
    - U.S. - Netherlands
    - U.S. - Russia
  - Relief
  - Religion
  - Religious ( Life)
  - Rembrandt
  - Remer, C. F.
  - Remey, Mason
  - Reminiscences, items to write
  - Renchard, G. W.
  - Reparation
  - "Repatriation"
  - Representation
  - Representation, diplomatic
  - Representation by U.S. Government of interests of one country in third country
  - Republican campaign
  - Republican Women, League of, School of Politics, "Conduct Foreign Relations,", 1930 (Box 362)
  - Research, subsidies for
  - Research, suggestions for
  - Research, Who's Who in
  - Reservations, precedents for
  - Reserve Officers' Association
  - Reserve Officers' Association, Constitution of
  - "Het Residentie Orkest"
  - "Resignation" (Special)
  - Resignation as American Clerk at the Nanking Consulate
  - Resources, United States
  - Restitution
  - Retirement
  - Reversible Collar Company
  - Reybold, Capt. John B.
  - Reynard, W. E.
  - Reynolds, Conger
  - Reynolds, Lincoln
  - Reynolds, Robert R.
  - Rhee, Syngman
  - Rhoads, Charles J.
  - Rhodes, Cecil
  - Rhodes scholars
    - General
    - Association
    - In Massachusetts
    - Hamilton, G. E. for the Oxonian (Box 363)
    - Scholarship trust
    - Scholarships, 1916-1927
    - Subject folder
    - Scholarships, 1929-1933 (Box 364)
    - Reunion, 1929, 1933
    - Scholarships, 1950 (Box 365)
    - Exams, etc., 1952
    - 1953 May
    - Scholarships, 1952-1954
    - The American Oxonian, price list for reprints
    - Association of American Rhodes Scholars, Constitution
    - Class of 1904, the active, manuscript
    - Reunion, Swarthmore, 1965 June 18-20
    - Selection, 1963 December
    - Selection, 1964
    - Selection Committee, 1965 December
    - D.C. roster
    - 1965-1966
    - General
    - Rice, Charles (Box 366)
  - Rice, Edward E.
  - Rice, Elwood E.
  - Rice, Stuart A.
  - Rich, John F.
  - Rich, Raymond T., World Peace Foundation
  - Richardson, Garland
  - Richardson, James
  - Richardson, Norval, "My Diplomatic Education"
  - Richardson, Robert C.
  - Richardson, W. Garland
  - Richey, Lawrence
  - Richmond, Indiana (William C. Dennis), 1950
  - Rickover, Adm. H. G.
  - Riddell, Guy C.
  - Ridder, J.
  - Rigby, Cora
  - Riggs, B. Reath
  - Riggs National Bank
  - Rights
  - Rights, A Declaration of
  - Riley, Julian
  - Rinehart, Stanley M.
  - Ringer, Gordon
  - Ringwalt, Arthur R.
  - Riots
  - Rivers, William C.
  - Robbins, Warren D.
  - Roberts, Owen F.
  - Robertson, C. H.
  - Robertson, David A.
  - Robertson, Walter
  - Robins, H. M.
  - Robinson, Dorothy
  - Robinson, Jacob
  - Robinson, Leland R.
  - Robinson, Thomas H.
  - Rochford, Daniel
  - Rock, Dr. Joseph F.
  - Rock Creek Women's Republican Club, 1961
  - Rockefeller, John D.
  - Rockefeller, Nelson
  - Rodgers, Rear Admiral W. L., "Diplomacy"
  - Rodgers, William L.
  - Rogers, Alan
  - Rogers, Edith Nourse
  - Rogers, Fred F.
  - Rogers, James Grafton
  - Rogers, James Harvey
  - Rogers, Leighton W.
  - Rogers, L. "America's Case Against Germany"
  - Rogers, Theo
  - Rogers, Walter S.
  - Rolfe, Mary A. (Box 367)
  - Romig, Joseph A.
  - Romijn, Cornelis Theo
  - Romney, Gov.
  - Romulo, Carlos P.
  - Romulo on Asia
  - Rookmaker, E. Tj.
  - Roos, Robert A.
  - Roosevelt and Churchill
  - Roosevelt, Edith K.
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., President
  - Roosevelt genealogy
  - Roosevelt, James
  - Roosevelt, Kermit
  - Roosevelt Library, Drewry, 1966
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas "Making a New China out of War-Torn Nation,", 1928
  - Roosevelt, Theodore
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr.
  - Roosevelts
  - Root, Elihu
  - Root-Takahira Agreement
  - Roots, John, on China Policy, circa 1948 (Box 368)
  - Roots, Logan H.
  - Roper, Daniel C.
  - Roper, Elmo
  - Roseberg, Evar
  - Roseman, Alvin
  - Rosenman Mission
  - Rosinki, Herbert
  - Ross, Ben
  - Ross, H. F.
  - Rosse, G. W.
  - Rostow
  - Roszel, B. M., 2.0 folders)
  - Rotterdam
  - Roumanian Legation
  - Round Table
  - Rowbotham, A.
  - Rowe, David N.
  - Rowe, David, on U.S. and Asia, 1949
  - Roue, Leo S.
  - Rowell, Chester Harvey
  - Rowland, Charles A.
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs
  - Roye, Harry
  - Rubber
  - Rubber, 1940, 1942
  - Rubel, L. E.
  - Ruddock, A. B.
  - Ruess, W.
  - Rugg, Charles B.
  - Rumford Press
  - Rush-Bagot Agreement of 1817
  - Rusk, Dean, 1950-1963; 4.0 folders)
  - Russell, Bertrand
  - Russell, Charles A.
  - Russell, Donald
  - Russell, Franklin
  - Russell, John Forbes
  - Russian East Asia
  - Rutherford, Forrest S.
  - Ruthlad, Mary
  - Ryan, the Rt. Rev. James Hugh (Bishop of Omaha)
  - Ryan, James W.
  - Ryan, Martin A.
  - Ryan, W. R.
  - Saburi, Sadas (Box 369)
  - Sachs, Alexander
  - Saffer, Charles
  - Sahara, T.
  - Saint John's Church
  - Saionji, Prince Kimmochi
  - Sakatani
  - Sakatani Incident
  - Salaries
  - Salinger, Edgar
  - Salisbury, Laurence E.
  - Salmon, David A.
  - Salter, Arthur and Ethel
  - Salter, Fred K.
  - Salvador
  - Salvation Army
  - Salvesen, H. K.
  - Sammons, T.
  - Samoa
  - Samoa and New Zealand
  - Samson, Gerald
  - San Antonio Express
  - San Francisco Chronicle
  - Sanavitis, Anthony
  - Sanborn, Design for War Review by Bemis
  - Sanctions, 2.0 folders)
  - Sanctions, economic
  - Sandberg, H. W.
  - Sanders, Jack Howard
  - Sands, Edwin (Box 370)
  - Sands, William Franklin
  - Sansom, Sir George
  - Santa Claus
  - Sard, Abbie Ingalls
  - Sard, Russell E.
  - Sarnoff Plan, 1955 May
  - Satellites
  - Satire
  - Sato, Ken
  - Satterthwaite, Livingston
  - Saturday Evening Post
  - Saturday Evening Post (Mr. Frederic Nelson), 1954
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1961 July
  - Saudi Arabia
  - Savage, Carlton
  - Savitsch, Eugene de
  - Sawada, S.
  - Sawyer, Charles
  - Sawyer, George
  - Sayre, Francis
  - Scalapino and Conlon Associates
  - Schaffner, Margaret A.
  - Schain, Josephine, "Cause and Cure of War"
  - Schecklen, George F.
  - Scheeline, Julia G.
  - Schenkman, Irvin
  - Scherbak, H.
  - Scherer, James A. B.
  - Schick, Leonard H.
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr.
  - Schmitt, Bernadotte E.
  - Schmitt, Bernadotte E. (Box 371)
  - Schmitt: Europe
  - Schnapper, M. B.
  - Schnare, Lester L.
  - Schneider, Helen
  - Schneider, President Herman
  - Schock, H. C.
  - Schoenfeld, Rudolf E.
  - Scholes, Prof. Walter V., 1966
  - Scholte, Daphne W.
  - Scholz, Richard F.
  - Schoonheim, H.
  - Schroder, Hans Jurgen
  - Schuirmann, Captain Roscoe E.
  - Schuler, Frank A., Jr.
  - Schultheis, Dorothy
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould
  - Schwager, Charles
  - Schwandt, Robert
  - Schwartz, Harry, "Two Lenins," NYT Magazine, 1963 July 14
  - Schwellenbach, Lewis B. (Washington)
  - Science
  - Scientists
  - Scott, Almere L.
  - Scott, Blair
  - Scott, the Reverend Charles Ernest
  - Scott, James Brown
  - Scott Resolution
  - Scott, Rey
  - Scotten, R.
  - Scranton (Box 372)
  - Scrap iron
  - Scribe, the (re Egypt), Vol. I, No. 1
  - Scribner Book Store
  - Sea Island
  - Seaman's Church Institute of New York
  - Sears Roebuck
  - Sears Roebuck, 1955
  - Southeast Asia Treaty Organization
  - Seavey, Warren A.
  - Sebald, William
  - Secker, Walter
  - Secretary of State
    - Unfinished
    - Press interviews with
    - 1932-1934 (Box 373)
    - Messages from and to Minister Hirota, 1934
    - China-Japan statement, 1935 December 5
    - 1935-1937, 3.0 folders)
    - Eight Pillars of Peace Statement, 1937 July 16
    - Statement, 1937 August 23
    - Speech at National Press Club, 1938 March 17 (Box 374)
    - 1938-1939, 2.0 folders)
    - Address, 1940 February 29 (Box 375)
    - Address, 1940 October 26
    - Address, 1940 November 1
    - Address, 1940 November 5
    - 1940
    - 1941, 4.0 folders) (Box 376)
    - 1942, 3.0 folders) (Box 377)
    - Lincoln Day Speech, 1942
    - 1943, 3.0 folders) (Box 378)
    - Drafts of Secretary's address, 1943 September 11
    - Memoranda summarizing situation in the Far East, 1943; 2.0 folders) (Box 379)
    - 1944, 4.0 folders) (Box 380)
    - Security (Box 381)
  - Security Storage Co.
  - Sedgley, Isabel
  - Sedgwick, Ellery
  - See, F. S.
  - Seelt, H. G. N.
  - Segregation
  - Segsworth, B. C.
  - Seibert, Edwin L.
  - Seibert, Elvin
  - Seibold, Louis
  - Selective Service Regulations
  - Self-determination
  - Semantics
  - Semenoff, Ataman
  - Senate
  - Senate (Theodore Green)
  - Sense
  - Seret-Sijthoff, Mrs. J. L.
  - Servants
  - Service, John
  - Sevensma, Tietse Pieter
  - Sex
  - Sforza, Carlo
  - Shang Cheng, General
  - Shanghai Evening Post and Mercury
  - Shanghai
    - General
    - International settlement
    - International status
    - Peace conference
    - Situation, 1932; 2.0 folders) (Box 382)
    - Thirty-first Infantry
  - Shanghai Tiffin Club
  - Shanghai Tiffin Club, Hornbeck talk, 1955 December 13
  - Shanhaikwan
  - Shantung
    - General
    - 1914
    - January 27-28, official
    - April 22, morning
    - April 22, afternoon
    - Full explanation by Williams to White
    - Agreements and diplomatic record, texts
    - Clauses, Austrian Treaty, original
    - Congressional Record, 1920 March 3-4
    - Decision, effects of, Peace Conference, Peking
    - Decision, official statement, Baker
    - Decision at Paris Peace Conference
    - Disposal of
    - Miscellaneous
    - Our proposals (Box 383)
    - Protest of Chinese Delegation
    - Question
    - Question, miscellaneous memoranda to Williams and Baker
    - Railway, status
    - Recommendations to commissioner
    - Reinsch protests
    - Chapter VI, Temperley
    - Chapter VI, Temperley, miscellaneous pages
    - Treaty Provisions and Explanation
    - Uchida and Wilson, 1919 August
  - Shantung Christian University
  - Shantz, Harold
  - Shao, Otis, 1957 January
  - Shapiro, David
  - Sharp, Frank C.
  - Sharratt (H. F.) Storage Co.
  - Sharry, L.
  - Shaw, Albert
  - Shaw, G. Howland
  - Shaw, G. Howland, "unfinished"
  - Shaw, K. W.
  - Shaw, Roger
  - Shecklen, George F.
  - Sheehy, Maurice S.
  - Sheil, Mrs. William (Ruth B.)
  - Sheldon, Charles Stuart
  - Shelley, Commodore T.
  - Shepard, W. J., American Political Science Association Program, 1927
  - Shepardson, Whitney H. (Box 384)
  - Shepherd, Francis E. A.
  - Shepherd, George A., Address at Shanghai Tiffin Club, New York, 1937
  - Shepherd, George A.
  - Sherertz, D. L.
  - Sherman, Rose
  - Sherman, Thomas F.
  - Sherover, Max
  - Sherrill, Charles H.
  - Sherwell, G. Butler
  - Sherwood, H.
  - Shibata
  - Shibboleths
  - Shidehara, Baron
  - Shih Hu, Dr.
  - Shipley, Ruth B.
  - Shipstead, Senator Henrik (Minnesota)
  - Shiratori, Toshio
  - Shirts and collars
  - Shoemaker, Col. Henry W.
  - Shortridge, L. Virginia
  - Shortt, Adam
  - Shotwell, James T.
  - Shudian, Guozi
  - Siam (Box 385)
    - General, 3.0 folders)
    - 1918
    - Bibliography
    - Clippings
    - Collet
    - Commercial Treaty, MacMurray to Hornbeck, 1921
    - Extraterritoriality
    - Finance
    - Foreign Service
    - King and Queen Visit United States, 1931
    - Legal status of foreigners (Box 386)
    - Miscellaneous
    - Order of White Elephant
    - "Paring Down Siam," H. A. Gibbons
    - Sayre, "Siam's Fight for Sovereignty"
    - Tariff
    - Tariff and trade bibliography
    - Trade of Bangkok, 1918-1919
    - Treaty
    - Treaty Clauses, drafts of
    - Treaties
    - Treaties, Case for Revision of, 1919
    - U.S. Treaty of 1920
    - U.S. Treaty of 1921